噢 刚才那个台 往回调
Ah! Go back! Go back!
天啊
Geez.
你说的是真真
You speak the true-true.
天啊 老爸 你出演了《云图》
Oh, my god. Dad"s in "Cloud Atlas"!
Cloud Atlas 《云图》 12年美国电影
我出演了《云图》
I'm in "Cloud Atlas"!
《云图》是啥
What's "Cloud Atlas"?
有时候小真真
Sometimes, small true-true
不同于大真真
Different than the big true-true.
这怎么可能
How is this possible?
无限种时空就会有无限种可能
Infinite timelines, infinite possibilities,
自然会有某个时空Jerry是电影明星
Including a timeline where jerry's a movie star.
你们简直瞎激动
Look, you guys are getting excited about
完全不明白这个装置意义何在
the wrong aspect to this device.
看这个
Wha-look at this.
新一集"快快悬疑案"
And now, another quick mystery.
我只想知道 是谁能干出这种事
I just want to know who could have done something like this.
简直是人性的扭曲
It's a travesty.
是我干的
I did.
这是一把带血的刀
See this knife and all the blood on it?